{
    "id": "6b30dbbe7721452faf43f6549823baf1",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Martin ……………….. in his garage.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about actions and situations that are going on at the moment of speaking.",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works",
                "is working",
                "are working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Martin ………………. fixing things.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about our habits, preferences, hobbies etc.",
            "answers": [
                "enjoy",
                "enjoys",
                "is enjoying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What ………………… for breakfast?",
            "description": "If the arrangement already exists, we use the present continuous to talk about the future.",
            "answers": [
                "do we have",
                "are we having",
                "does we have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. France this summer.",
            "description": "If the arrangement already exists, we use the present continuous to talk about the future.",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "am visiting",
                "are visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. France every summer.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about our habits and routines.  ",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "visits",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. on any new projects at the moment?",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about actions and situations that are going on at the moment of speaking.",
            "answers": [
                "Do you work",
                "Are you working",
                "Is you working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………. on Sundays?",
            "description": "The question is about habits or routines.",
            "answers": [
                "Do you work",
                "Are you working",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How often ……………….. ?",
            "description": "The question is about habits or routines.",
            "answers": [
                "are you working out",
                "do you work out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie …………….. here often.",
            "description": "The statement is about habits or routines. ",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "comes",
                "is coming"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. with us to the movies?",
            "description": "The question is about arrangement that already exists.",
            "answers": [
                "Do you come",
                "Are you coming"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. what ……………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Is she knowing, she is doing",
                "Does she know, she does",
                "Does she know, she is doing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………. a washing machine?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you starting",
                "do you start",
                "does you start"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}